{
    "cards": [
        {
            "number": "251",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What island are you on if you're in Montego Bay?",
                "answer": "Jamaica"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What superheroine was known as Princess Diana before she left Paradise Island?",
                "answer": "Wonder Woman"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What article of clothing is a 'mackintosh', named for Scottish inventor Charles Macintosh?",
                "answer": "A raincoat"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "Which side of a boy's shirt are buttons on?",
                "answer": "The right"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "What animal's name means 'river horse'?",
                "answer": "The hippopotamus's"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "Could the fastest human swimmer keep up with a dolphin over one length of a pool?",
                "answer": "No"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "217",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "Is the North Pole in Canada?",
                "answer": "No"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "Who's the scientific genius of the Legion of Super-Heroes?",
                "answer": "Brainiac 5"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What's a 'rood' - a measure of area, distance, or weight?",
                "answer": "Area"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What shape is a dunce's cap",
                "answer": "Cone-shaped"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "What mammal can hold its breath the longest - the bottle-nosed whale, camel, or raccoon?",
                "answer": "The bottle-nosed whale (2 hours)"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "How much money does a player receive for landing on a Lucky Day space in 'Game of Life'?",
                "answer": "$10,000"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "120",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "Which Louis reigned as King of France for a record 72 years - Louis XIV, XV, or XVI?",
                "answer": "Louis XIV"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What musical candies does Dr. Potts invent in the movie 'Chitty Chitty Bang Bang'?",
                "answer": "Toot Sweets"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "Where's an 'amphicar' designed for traveling - on land and in the water, in space or in the Arctic?",
                "answer": "On land and in the water"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What's Gitchi Manitou - an Algonquin god, an Indian feast dish or an Eskimo medicine man?",
                "answer": "An Algonquin God"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "How many times a year does the human heart beat - more than 16 million, 26 million, or 36 million",
                "answer": "More than 36 million"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "How many cards are there in a Uno deck?",
                "answer": "108"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "160",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What language does 'merci' mean 'thank you' in?",
                "answer": "French"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What famed Russian ballet dancer appeared in the movie 'The Turning Point'?",
                "answer": "Mikhail Baryshnikov"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What's a 'sampan' usually powered by - a long pole, an outboard motor or two short oars?",
                "answer": "Two short oars"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What color rabbit does Alice follow down the hole to Wonderland?",
                "answer": "White"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "How many bones do most cats have in their tails - 10, 15, or 20?",
                "answer": "Twenty"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "What toy 'cracks the whip', does a 'front flip', and 'goes over the mountain'?",
                "answer": "The yo-yo"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "297",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What state's captial is Concord?",
                "answer": "New Hampshire's"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What fish are often used as a topping on pizzas?",
                "answer": "Anchovies"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "Does the Earth, viewed from above the North Pole, move in a clockwise or counterclockwise direction?",
                "answer": "Counterclockwise"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What Jewish holiday commemorates the freeing of Isrealites from slavery in Egypt?",
                "answer": "Passover"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "What kind of tigers lived in prehistoric times?",
                "answer": "Saber-toothed tigers"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "What kind of hobbyist uses a draw knife?",
                "answer": "A woodworker"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "180",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What city did Gustave Eiffel build a tower in?",
                "answer": "Paris"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What circus performers are called 'Joeys'?",
                "answer": "Clowns"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What's the term for the hole that's made when a meteor hits a planet or moon?",
                "answer": "Crater"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What fat, sea-going animal does ALice hear about in 'Through the Looking Glass'?",
                "answer": "The walrus"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "How many legs does a slowworm lizard have?",
                "answer": "Zero (It looks like a worm)"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "Which kind of skiers ski against the clock through a series of 'gates' - cross country skiers or slalom racers?",
                "answer": "Slalom racers"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "170",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What New England state was the last of the original 13 to join the Union?",
                "answer": "Rhode Island"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What's the nickname of John Entwhistle of The Who?",
                "answer": "The Ox"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What's the continuous flame that burns in appliances fueled by natural gas called?",
                "answer": "The pilot light"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What's the only food that Christopher Robin's friend Tigger likes to eat?",
                "answer": "Extract of malt"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "What's a male whale called?",
                "answer": "A bull"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "How many pieces does each player have at the start of a game of chess?",
                "answer": "Sixteen"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "277",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What were members of the National Socialist German Workers' Party better known as?",
                "answer": "Nazis"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "Is there a picture of a dad on \"Dad's\" cookie boxes?",
                "answer": "No"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "Is an asteroid smaller or larger than a planet?",
                "answer": "Smaller"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What saint rescued a princess who was about to be eaten by a dragon?",
                "answer": "Saint George"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "Which one does 90 percent of the hunting - the male or female lion?",
                "answer": "The female"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "Why does a backpacker carry dehydrated food instead of canned food?",
                "answer": "Because it's lighter"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "267",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What three colors make up the Italian flag?",
                "answer": "Green, red, white"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What cartoon character did Walt Disney once describe as 'a nice fellow who never does anybody any harm'?",
                "answer": "Mickey Mouse"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What did Sigmund Freud call 'the guardian of sleep'?",
                "answer": "Dreams"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What's the Mona Lisa doing - laughing, smiling, or winking?",
                "answer": "Smiling"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "What are poisonous mushrooms called?",
                "answer": "Toadstools"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "How many wheels does a skateboard have?",
                "answer": "Four"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "247",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "How old was Edmund Hillary when he climbed Mount Everest - 34, 54, or 74?",
                "answer": "34"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What TV show features Blair, Jo, Natalie, and Tootie?",
                "answer": "The Facts of Life"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What's the term for the instrument doctors use to listen to the sound inside the body?",
                "answer": "Stethoscope"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What did Yankee Doodle call the feather he stuck in his cap?",
                "answer": "Macaroni"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "Which lion does most of the hunting - the male or the female?",
                "answer": "The female"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "Which way does the king of spades face in a standard deck of cards?",
                "answer": "Right"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "227",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What explorer discovered Florida - Gasper Corte-Real, Pedro Alvarez Cabral or Juan Ponce de Leon?",
                "answer": "Juan Ponce de Leon"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What country does the movie 'Born Free' take place in?",
                "answer": "Kenya"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What does a Schmidt camera take photographs of - germs, plants, or the stars?",
                "answer": "The stars"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "Who cries: 'Happy Christmas to all, and to all a good night' - Rumpelstiltskin, Saint Nick, or Tiny Tim?",
                "answer": "Saint Nick"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "What are Calico Fans, Black Mollys and Tiger Barbs?",
                "answer": "Tropical fish"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "How many pieces of leather makeup an official softball?",
                "answer": "Two"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "294",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What member of a Middle Ages court carried a rattle and wore a cap with donkey's ears?",
                "answer": "The court jester"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What Walt Disney movie has the same name as a strange gravity whirlpool in space?",
                "answer": "The Black Hole"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "Who developed the first rabies vaccine - Thomas Edison, Louis Pasteur, or Joseph Priestley?",
                "answer": "Louis Pasteur"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What does a 'teetotaler' refuse to drink?",
                "answer": "Alcohol"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "How many fillets come from one fish?",
                "answer": "Two"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "What's the long straight part of a fishing hook called - the shaft, shank, or skirt?",
                "answer": "The shank"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "171",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "Where were kites invented - China, Japan, or Mexico?",
                "answer": "China"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What's the name of the vehicle that carries Strawberry Shortcake and her friends around Strawberry Land?",
                "answer": "Big Berry Trolley"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What's a 'calliope' - a cooking utensil, musical instrument, or old-fashioned hot tub?",
                "answer": "A musical instrument"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What city do the Darling children live in, in 'Peter Pan'?",
                "answer": "London"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "How many eyelids do birds have on each eye?",
                "answer": "Three"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "What star player led Brazil to an unprecedented third World Cup soccer victory?",
                "answer": "Pele"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "161",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What country's flag is made up of a red circle on a white background?",
                "answer": "Japan's"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What kind of hat does Yosemite Sam wear while feuding with Bugs Bunny?",
                "answer": "An oversized cowboy hat"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "How many days are there in a Leap Year?",
                "answer": "366"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What's the last name of the Three Billy Goats?",
                "answer": "Gruff"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "What multicolored pearl is often inlaid in Mexican silver jewelry?",
                "answer": "Mother-of-pearl"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "What National Football League team once boasted the Steel Curtain defense?",
                "answer": "The Pittsburgh Steelers"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "224",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What country's government-controlled news agency is called Tass?",
                "answer": "The Soviet Union's"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "Who is HAL's programmer in '2001: A Space Odyssey' - Mr. Hope, Mr. Langley, or Mr. Smith?",
                "answer": "Mr. Langley"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What toothpaste claims to help stop catvities before they start?",
                "answer": "Colgate"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What Dr. Seuss elephant hatches a bird's egg?",
                "answer": "Horton"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "How do seals get air while under water - by holding their breath, from a sac in their heads or through breathing holes in the ice?",
                "answer": "Through breathing holes in the ice"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "How many minutes long is a hooking penalty in hockey?",
                "answer": "Two"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "274",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What parallel of latitude divides much of Canada from the US - the 39th, 49th, or 59th?",
                "answer": "The 49th"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What type of spicy sausage is often served on pizzas?",
                "answer": "Pepperoni"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What kind of wind blows a comet's tail into space?",
                "answer": "Solar Wind"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What two brothers named Jacob and Wilhelm collected fairy tales?",
                "answer": "The Brothers Grimm"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "Which has more teeth - a dog or a cat?",
                "answer": "A dog"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "Is it a fault in tennis if the server catches the ball instead of hitting it after throwing it up?",
                "answer": "No"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "191",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What famous captain of the 'Bounty' became governor of New South Wales, Australia?",
                "answer": "William Bligh"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What producer-director-actor worked on 'Young Frankenstein', 'Blazing Saddles', and 'History of the World, Part I'?",
                "answer": "Mel Brooks"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What timely device was Louis Cartier the first to make, in 1904?",
                "answer": "The wristwatch"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What does Beauty's father steal from the Beast?",
                "answer": "A rose"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "Does the cone-bearing eastern larch, or tamarack, lose its needles in the fall and go naked through the winter?",
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "What puffy pants are worn for horseback riding?",
                "answer": "Jodhpurs"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "244",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "How many states does California border?",
                "answer": "3"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "How many men are there in the rock group Kiss?",
                "answer": "4"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What common household appliance boasts a 'bread carriage'?",
                "answer": "A toaster"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What, according to the poem, can you use to keep peas on your knife?",
                "answer": "Honey"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "Which is bigger - a bicycle wheel or the bloom of a large stinking corpse lily?",
                "answer": "The bloom of a large stinking corpse lily"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "Is it better to tie up to dock's lee ide or windward side?",
                "answer": "Its lee side"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "264",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What are the Kalahari, Sahara, and Namib?",
                "answer": "Deserts"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "Where do TV's Jessie Brewer, Amy Vining, Ruby Anderson and Bobbie Spencer work?",
                "answer": "General Hospital"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What does the abbreviation 'Inc.' mean at the end of a company's name?",
                "answer": "Incorporated"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What are the names of the three Darling children in 'Peter Pan'?",
                "answer": "John, Michael, Wendy"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "Which one is a primary color - blue, green, or orange?",
                "answer": "Blue"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "What are backpackers talking about when they say: 'If you carried it in, you can carry it out'?",
                "answer": "Garbage"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "133",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What early President called the job 'a splendid misery'?",
                "answer": "Thomas Jefferson"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What food company makes noodle animals called Zoodles?",
                "answer": "Libby's"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What does a zoologist study?",
                "answer": "Animals"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "Where did 'Peter, Peter, Pumpkin Eater' put his wife when he couldn't keep her?",
                "answer": "In a pumpkin shell"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "Which is wider in humans - the small instestine or the large intestine?",
                "answer": "The large intestine"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "What sport is Ralph Lauren known for - bowling, lacrosse, or polo?",
                "answer": "Polo"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "231",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What portly President hanged a man while serving as a sheriff in Buffalo?",
                "answer": "Grover Cleveland"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What singer-actor was the song Edelweiss written for - Theodore Bikel, Gene Kelly, or Christopher Plummer?",
                "answer": "Theodore Bikel"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "Where would you be if you were in a 'dhow' - on land, in the water or in the air?",
                "answer": "In the water"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "Which instrument isn't played with a bow - the double bass, harp, or violin",
                "answer": "The harp"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "What's the largest tiger in the world - the Bengal tiger, Siberian tiger, or Tasmanian tiger?",
                "answer": "The Siberian tiger"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "How many peg holes are there in a row in a regular game of 'Master Mind'?",
                "answer": "Four"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "183",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What continent would you find the Mountains of the Moon on - Africa, Asia, or Europe?",
                "answer": "Africa"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What color is the K on a box of Kellog's Special K?",
                "answer": "Red"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What did most people in Galileo's time think was the center of the universe?",
                "answer": "Earth"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "Why did Count Dracula consider mirrors a dead giveaway?",
                "answer": "Vampires have no reflection"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "What vegetable has a 'sweet banana' variety?",
                "answer": "The pepper"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "What piece of sailing equipment has corners described as 'head', 'tack' and 'clew'?",
                "answer": "A sail"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "281",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What member of the Kennedy family was the first elected to the Senate in 1962?",
                "answer": "Teddy Kennedy"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What color is the character Croc in the comic strip 'Animal Crackers'?",
                "answer": "Green"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What country builds the most bicycles each year?",
                "answer": "The United States"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What does Old Mother Hubbard hope to fetch from the cupboard for her dog - a biscuit, a bone, or a leash?",
                "answer": "A bone"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "What vegetable 'bleeds' if all the stalk are cut off before cooking?",
                "answer": "The beet"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "What can be made by dipping, pouring, or casting?",
                "answer": "Candles"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "138",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What's the capital of the Soviet Union?",
                "answer": "Moscow"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "Who does Daniel J. Travanti play on TV's 'Hill Street Blues'?",
                "answer": "Frank Furillo"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What kind of outdoor clock has no moving parts?",
                "answer": "A sundial"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What date is Boxing Day observed on?",
                "answer": "December 26th"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "Is Earth's core solid, liquid, or both",
                "answer": "Both"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "How many minutes long is a misconduct penalty in hockey?",
                "answer": "Ten"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "240",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What European country's people call an expressway an 'autostrada'?",
                "answer": "Italy's"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "Does the 'Planter`s Peanuts' man wear glasses, a monocole, or contact lenses?",
                "answer": "A monocole"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "Which pedal is in the middle in a car with standard transmission - the accelerator, brake, or clutch?",
                "answer": "The brake"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "What's left after Pandora lets all the evil things out of her box?",
                "answer": "Hope"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "Are you standing or sitting if you put your coccyx on the floor?",
                "answer": "Sitting (The coccyx is the tail bone)"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "Does the hammer thrown in the Olympic hammer event have a wooden handle?",
                "answer": "No"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "211",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "What's the world's largest fresh-water lake?",
                "answer": "Lake Superior"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What color is Yogi Bear's hat?",
                "answer": "Green"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "What kind of chair lets a baby see eye-to-eye with adults?",
                "answer": "A highchair"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "How many angels keep watch over the child in the opera 'Hansel and Gretel' - 10, 14, or 18?",
                "answer": "14"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "What are 'Stilton', 'Double Gloucester', 'Cheshire', and 'Wensleydale'?",
                "answer": "Kinds of cheese"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "What kind of shoes come in Alaskan and Michigan styles?",
                "answer": "Snowshoes"
            }
        },
        {
            "number": "290",
            "ype_PP": {
                "question": "Which isn't a real place - Bikini Atoll or No Bikini Atoll?",
                "answer": "No Bikini Atoll"
            },
            "ype_GT": {
                "question": "What studio made the movie 'Bambi'?",
                "answer": "Disney"
            },
            "ype_ST": {
                "question": "Do divers wear suits to keep dry?",
                "answer": "No"
            },
            "ype_AC": {
                "question": "Which of Brobdingnag, Lilliput and Slobbovia does Gulliver NOT visit?",
                "answer": "Slobbovia"
            },
            "ype_NW": {
                "question": "What do badgers live in - flets, nets, or setts?",
                "answer": "Setts"
            },
            "ype_GH": {
                "question": "What's a person who's playing the Bulldog Drummond doing - playing cards, flying a kite or training a dog?",
                "answer": "Flying a kite"
            }
        }
    ]
}